For the examples in this course,
للحصول على الأمثلة في هذه الدورة التدريبية،
we'll use data from Parch and Posey,
سنستخدم البيانات من Parch وPosey،
a company that sells paper.
شركة متخصصة في بيع الورق.
They have 50 sales reps spread across the United States in four regions.
لديهم 50 مندوب مبيعات منتشرون على مستوى أربع مناطق في الولايات المتحدة.
They sell three types of paper: regular, poster, and glossy.
يبيعون ثلاثة أنواع من الورق: العادي والملصقات واللامع.
Their clients are primarily large Fortune 100 companies
يمثل العملاء ثروة كبيرة لديهم، عبارة عن 100 شركة
whom they attract by advertising on Google, Facebook, and Twitter.
حيث يجذبون العملاء بالإعلانات على Google وFacebook وTwitter.
Parch and Posey is not a real company.
Parch وPosey ليست شركة حقيقية.
We fabricated it and all of these data for the sake of this course.
اختلقناها هي وكل هذه البيانات لأغراض هذه الدورة التدريبية.
The questions you'll answer using Parch and Posey's data
لذا فالأسئلة التي ستجاوبون عنها باستخدام بيانات Parch وPosey
are meant to simulate real world problems.
تهدف إلى محاكاة مشاكل العالم الواقعي.
Using SQL, we will be able to help Parch and Posey answer tricky questions like,
باستخدام SQL سنكون قادرين على مساعدة Parch وPosey في الإجابة عن الأسئلة الخادعة مثل،
which of their product lines is worst performing?
أي خطوط الإنتاج الأسوأ أداءً؟
Or, which of their marketing channels they should make a greater investment in?
أو، أي القنوات التسويقية عليهم الاستثمار فيها بشكل أكبر؟